https://www.gilca.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentThis notice explains how we will process your personal information.Data Protection PrinciplesGilca Limited complies with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003. The eight principles relating to the processing of personal information are:Personal data shall be processed fairly and lawfullyPersonal data shall be obtained only for one or more specified and lawful purposesPersonal data shall be adequate, relevant and not excessive in relation to the purpose or purposes for which they are processedPersonal data shall be accurate and, where necessary, kept up to datePersonal data processed for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessaryPersonal data shall be processed in accordance with the rights of data subjects under this ActAppropriate technical and organisational measures shall be taken against unauthorised or unlawful processing of personal data and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, personal dataPersonal data shall not be transferred to a country or territory outside the European Economic Area unless that country or territory ensures an adequate level of protection for the rights and freedoms of data subjects in relation to the processing of personal dataYour privacy and security is of utmost importance to us. We will always follow these principles and ask you how you would like us to communicate with you. The Information Commissioner regulates compliance with the Data Protection Act. See details at end of this page.Why we collect your data?By collecting your data, it allows us to understand what your needs and wants are. It also allows us to provide targeted offers and services you may be interested to hear about.Cookies and IP AddressesA cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and to identify users returning to a website.Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies. A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date). A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.Essential Cookies
These cookies are essential for the running of our websites. Without the use of these cookies parts of our websites would not function, these are typically used within contact forms or the secure login section of our site.Analytical CookiesWe use these types of cookies to monitor the usage of our website. These cookies provide us with information that helps us provide a better service / product to our customer, they also identify any areas that may need maintenance.Third Party CookiesWe may also track IP addresses. An IP Address is a number that can identify an Internet Service Provider and country location. It cannot provide personal information.How to control the use of cookiesYou are not obliged to accept cookies and may modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. The browser you use allows you to see cookies and control their use.You can control them by allowing them, deleting them individually or deleting all of them. You can also set your browser to not accept cookies altogether. If this option is selected, you should be aware that many websites will not function properly or at all. It may be possible to set your browser to not accept cookies and ask for your consent before each cookie is set on your device. This gives you control over what is set on your device, however has the drawback of slowing down your browsing experience.There are different levels of control too. You are able to prevent just third party cookies being deployed, effectively opting out of behavioural advertising, and some even allow you to block specific companies you do not wish to deploy a cookie, instead of selecting all companies.In order to manage your cookies, please select your browser from the list below and follow the instructions:ChromeFirefoxInternet ExplorerHow To Prevent Online Behavioural AdvertisingFurther to configuring your browser to control the use of cookies, there are also other ways that you can opt out of online behavioural advertising.The “Your Online Choices” page provided by the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB), provides an easy way to opt out of behavioural advertising from each (or all) of the networks represented by the IAB.Some more useful information about CookiesMore information about cookies can be found at the following websites:All About CookiesInformation Commissioners OfficeMicrosoft Cookies GuideYour Online ChoicesIf you have any questions about the use of cookies on our websites, please email: info@localhostMarketing consentIf you are an existing customer we will keep you informed of our latest news, products and services.When you give us your personal information, we will give you an option to receive additional on-going marketing communications from us.We do not sell our customer data to other companies.All of our marketing communications will have a method to unsubscribe. You may also exercise your right to opt out for marketing purposes at any time by contacting us by one of the methods explained at the end of this notice.DisclosureYour personal information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law to do so. If you post or send offensive or objectionable content anywhere on or to any of our websites or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on any of our websites, we can use the information that is available to us about you to stop such behaviour. This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour. Search for: Recent CommentsArchivesCategoriesNo categoriesMetaLog inEntries feedComments feedWordPress.orgBrexit Statement for GILCA Customers.Read More...Brexit Statement for GILCA Customers
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
